#### MUTUYIMANA Alice

Kigali - Nyarugenge, Phone Number: +250 782099213

Portfolio: <a href="https://mutuyimana-portifolio.netlify.app">https://mutuyimana-portifolio.netlify.app</a>

Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/Alice-Mutuyimana">https://www.linkedin.com/in/Alice-Mutuyimana</a> Email: <a href="mailto:amutuyimana64@gmail.com">amutuyimana64@gmail.com</a>

#### **RESUME**

I am a dedicated passionate software developer willing to face the current challenges and ready to learn new skills. I am a graduate form University of Rwanda College of Science and Technology (CST) in Information Technology (IT) and am extremely knowledgeable with experience in Project management, web application development, Data analysis and database management. I am a strongly reliable person and highly flexible means I can work with anyone in any community and also, I am a faster leaner.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Frontend Developer**

Feb 2022- May 2023

**SolvIT Africa** 

- Developed internal project called Airline Ticket Booking using JavaScript and React JS
- Lead team of 5 people toward the success of this project.

### Software developer

April 2022-Jan 2023 Igire Rwanda Organization

Developed IRO E-learning website which is responsible for help each and every one easy access to the programming courses. Technology used were JavaScript, React JS and Node JS.

### **Technical Facilitator**

June 2022- Present

**Igire Rwanda Organization** I worked as technical assistant facilitator at shecancode program of Igire Rwanda organization includes duties of:

- Serve as an instructor for an in-person program of Web development (JavaScript and React JS)
- Provide constructive feedback on students' assessment.

# ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

## **Thegym**

# 13 December 2022\_17 December 2022

I attended Code and Design program of thegym where I learn design using Figma and develop mobile app using thunkable.

**SHE-CAN-CODE** 

November 2021-January 2022

I attended shecancode training program I was trained software development (Node js, React JS, MongoDB,SQL and web deployment) and during program I develop website called Umurenge Quick.

BS University of Rwanda

Nov 2018-January 2022

Information Technology

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript View JS LANGUAGES	React JS	Node JS		Bootstrap	GitHub
English (Excellent)	Kinyarwanda (Excellent)				
REFERENCES					
Samuel RUTUNDA	CTO of Digital Umuganda	ı	+25078862310	7	
Harerimana Dominique	Information Technology I	IOD	+250785135124	ļ	
Iradukunda Jean Jacque	CEO OF Igire Rwanda		+25088737287		